我不想和你们一起乘车回去 我想摆脱挫败感
I don't wanna ride back with you guys. Rather go shake this off.
是 当然 没问题
Yeah, sure. No, of course.
嘿…路上小心 好吗
Hey. Hey, hey. Just-- Be careful out there, all right?
好的
Yeah? Okay.
别忘了
And don't forget,
明天轮到你负责准备看比赛视频时的咖啡
tomorrow it's your turn for coffee at the game film, all right?
-是 -明早见
-Yeah. -Bright and early.
嘿 教练 一步一步慢慢走
Hey, Coach. Bird by bird.
没让你竖中指
Not that kind of bird.
（温布利公园地铁站）
蓝月亮 你看到我独自彷徨
Blue moon You saw me standing alone
心中没有梦想
Without a dream in my heart
身边没有爱人
Without a love of my own
请小心站台间隙
Mind the gap.
这是向南开往阿尔德盖特的大都会线列车
This is the southbound metropolitan line train to Aldgate.
车门正在关闭 请勿靠近车门
Doors closing. Stand clear of the doors, please.
这样的时刻一个接着一个
It was moment after moment like this.
一场真正的小人物大卫挑战巨人的比赛
A real David versus Goliath match,
但是在这场比赛中 巨人轻而易举地击溃了大卫
but where Goliath just curb-stomped David in the back of the skull
就像那部爱德华诺顿电影
like in that Ed Norton movie.
《月升王国》
Moonrise Kingdom?
应该是的 对
I think that's it, yeah.
对 我认为这场比赛 是一个现实中的灰姑娘故事
Yeah. Well, for me, the match was a real Cinderella story.
只不过主角的玻璃鞋断了 然后把跟腱割断
If her glass slipper broke and sliced her Achilles tendon.
蒂埃里 球员们是否状态不好
Thierry, was this just an off day for the players?
（简佩恩）
还是应该归咎于教练组
Or do we lay the blame on the coaching staff?
完全是教练组的错
100% coaching staff.
球员们都很出色
Those are good footballers.
感觉里士满完全没有计划
It just felt like Richmond had no plan.
-彼尔德教练呢  -总算说到他了
-And what about Coach Beard? -What about him, indeed.
彼尔德教练知道 采取强势进攻策略是个错误
Coach Beard knew an aggressive offensive strategy was a mistake.
他不应该放任泰德、内森和罗伊一意孤行
He should not have let Ted, Nathan and Roy convince him otherwise.
说得好 蒂埃里 彼尔德教练是泰德拉索的副手
Great point, Thierry. Coach Beard is Ted Lasso's number two.
他应该敢于质疑他 而不是当个唯命是从的跟班
He's supposed to challenge him, not just be a sniveling lackey.
说实话 盖瑞 那家伙根本没有干劲
Look, Gary, the man has no va-va-voom.
有什么比棋盘咖啡桌 更能体现“悲惨单身汉”的东西吗
Does anything say "sad, single man" more than a chessboard coffee table?
我知道作为法国人 我说这种话并不出人意料
I know I'm French and expected to say things like this,
但我讨厌彼尔德教练
but I hate Coach Beard.
闭嘴吧 蒂埃里亨利
Shut up, Thierry Henry.
理查德蒙特劳被罚红牌后
After Richard Montlaur earned himself a red card,
情况变得更糟
things went from bad to worse.
泰德也会来吗
Ted joining you?
不会
No.
-简会来吗  -我们分手了
-Jane coming? -We broke up.
令人震惊
Shocking.
她指责我爱吃醋 我
She accused me of being jealous. Me.
因为我说很难了解她对我是什么感觉
Because I told her it's hard to know where I stand,
而这是真的 因为她从不说“我爱你”
which it is, because she never says "I love you."
-你对她说了吗  -说了
-Did you say it to her? -I did.
-而她没回应你 -她没有
-And she didn't say it back. -She did not.
多谢你让我又重温这一切
Thank you for helping me relive that.
你一定感到很难受
Well, you must feel awful.
在爱的表达上 理性没有任何力量
Reason is powerless in the expression of love.
不 我是说比赛
Nuh-uh. I meant about the match.
你是不是脑子进水了才想出那些战术
What the hell was your thinking behind those tactics?
-梅 -好吧 享受你的啤酒
-Mae. -All right. Enjoy your beer.
但是拜托
But come on.
你不可能认为进攻策略是个好主意
There's no way you thought coming out on the attack was a good idea.
你基本上让佐豪在后场独自防守
You basically left Zoreaux back there to defend by himself.
这可是半决赛
In a semifinal…
半决赛
A semifinal!
（简佩恩）
（我看到比分了 唉 来找我吗 ）
（你在哪里 ）
（我去夜店了）
（我把自己的感受告诉你了 我不能继续这样了）
（如果你不愿意说出你的感受）
喂 彼尔德 你的钥匙掉了
Oi, Beard. Dropped your keys.
谢谢
Thanks.
-今天的比赛真惨 哥们 -我们觉得你需要一个拥抱
-Rough match, mate. -We thought you needed a hug.
-我觉得你需要一个拥抱 -你想聊聊吗
-I thought you needed a hug. -Do you wanna talk about it?
我们可以边喝酒边聊
We can talk and drink
只要我们一边喝酒一边聊的不是比赛就好
as long as we talk about anything but the game and drink.
-你去过拉斯维加斯吗  -泰德私底下是什么样的
-Have you ever been to Vegas? -What's Ted like behind closed doors?
如何应对宇宙无穷无尽
How do you cope knowing the universe is infinite
但人的意识可能立即消失这点
but your consciousness can end in a second?
我去过很多次拉斯维加斯
I've been to Vegas many times.
在那里度过一晚很不错 两个晚上完美 三个晚上就太多了
One night is good, two nights is perfect, three is too many.
泰德也是普通人 仅此而已
Ted is a man. Just a man.
至于生命之脆弱 我很高兴终于有人问了这个问题
And as for the fragility of life, I'm so glad someone finally asked.
因为我有一些想法
Because, yeah, I got a few thoughts.
因此 总而言之
And so, in conclusion,
如果这个世界确实是一个虚拟程序
if this is all indeed a simulation,
从我所经历的一切看来 它的确是
which everything in my experience suggests that it is,
那么我们唯一能做的就是 向操控这一切的无赖脱帽致敬
then all we can do is tip our caps to the rascal pulling the strings.
好了 几位
That's it, people.
就如在和一个总纠正我的男人约会后 我双腿的状态一样
Just like my legs after a date with a guy who kept correcting me,
我们要关门了
we're closed.
你和理查德约会了
You went on a date with Richard?
梅 其实是两次约会
I think you'll find, Mae, it was two dates.
出去
Out.
喝咖啡也算一次约会
Coffee was a date.
（我觉得这是你需要的 我正为自己的过错赎罪）
（如果你不打算加入 我希望你至少玩得开心）
接下来去哪
Where to next?
睡觉 这里是英国 哥们 酒吧在11点30分就打烊
Bed. This is England, mate. Pubs shut at 11:30.
我没准备让今晚结束 有什么想法吗
Well, I'm not ready for the night to end. Any ideas?
去骨头与蜜糖如何
What about Bones & Honey?
想得美
As if.
那是私人酒吧 非常高档 不可能进得去
Private club, very swanky, impossible to get in.
听说他们曾把雪儿拒之门外
Yeah, I heard they once turned away Cher.
你能相信他们竟然这么做吗
Would you believe They did such a thing?
这个嘛…
Well…
不如我们先过去碰碰运气
Why don't we just head over there and see what happens?
那里似乎有着装要求
I think there's a dress code.
（失物招领）
梅 我爱你
Mae, I love you!
德士
Taxi!
-欢迎回来 亲爱的 -谢谢
-Welcome back, darling. -Thank you.
晚上好
Good evening.
我们认识吗
Do we know each other?
应该不认识 先生 请出示你的会员证 谢谢
I don't think we do, sir. May I see your membership card?
巴塞罗那大学2004级
University of Barcelona, class of 2004?
我是华威大学2007级的
I went to Warwick, 2007.
抱歉 你看起来年纪比较大
Sorry, you looked older.
你是这里的会员吗
Are you a member here?
这里 不 天啊 当然不是
Here? No. God, no. Never.
如果你不是会员 恐怕你不能进来
Well, if you're not a member, I'm afraid you can't come in.
这里可是骨头与蜜糖
This is Bones & Honey.
你很无礼
You are very rude.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
我叫莎拉库姆斯 你叫什么名字
My name is Sarah Coombes. What is your name?
关你屁事
None of my business.
骨头与蜜糖 请问有什么事
Bones & Honey, may I help you?
你能走开吗
Do you mind?
请说
Speak.
你好 我是消防队的
Hello, this is the fire brigade.
我们现在必须要联络上…
It's very important that we get in touch with--
-莎拉库姆斯 -莎拉库姆斯
-Sarah Coombes. -Sarah Coombes.
你就是啊
That's you.
是这样的 很遗憾 女士 你的公寓起火了
Well, I'm very sorry, madam, but your flat is on fire.
你必须立即过来这里
You need to come down here immediately.
-然后呢  -表现得酷一点
-Now what? -Act cool.
猎户座腰带
Orion's Belt!
真厉害
Amazing.
走吧…
We're walking. We're walking.
你成功了
You did it.
你做到了雪儿没做到的事
You did what Cher couldn't do.
其实我挺为莎拉库姆斯感到难过的
I actually feel bad for Sarah Coombes.
用不着 想一想她之后会有多开心
Nah. Think how excited she'll be
意识到自己的公寓没有真的起火
when she realizes that her place didn't actually burn down.
明天将是莎拉库姆斯人生中最美好的一天
Tomorrow will be the most beautiful day of Sarah Coombes's life.
在她的眼中 她的公寓
Her apartment will look more amazing to her
将比我们住过的任何地方都美
than any place any of us have ever lived.
到了
Here we go.
好的 先生们 进攻计划
Okay, gentlemen, plan of attack.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我觉得我们不属于这里
I don't think we belong here.
别这么想
Knock that shit off.
你们就属于这里
We belong.
如果能去任何地方 你们想去哪里
If you could be anywhere, where would you wanna be?
就是这里 对吗
Here, right?
那就表现出来
Then act like it.
谁想喝定价过高的啤酒
Now who wants an overpriced beer?
谁想喝定价过高的啤酒 我请客
Who wants an overpriced beer that I'm paying for?
去找个座位
Find us a spot.
还有…昂头挺胸
And feel free to strut.
先生 您想喝点什么
What can I get you, sir?
-四瓶啤酒 谢谢 -用玻璃杯装吗 先生
-Four beers, please. -Would you like them in glass, sir?
不用
No.
别紧张 兄弟 不过是看好角度
Relax, fella. It's just angles.
若你在三角课上留心听课 球会打得好一点
Maybe if you'd paid attention in trig, you'd do better.
这一球要不要赌一把
Shall we have a friendly wager on this shot?
赌20英镑
Say, 20 quid?
等等
Hold on.
三角课是什么
What's trig?
三角学课
Trigonometry.
数学 对吗
Maths. Yeah?
-是… -对
-Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah.
抱歉 你们在哪里读的书
Sorry, but where did you guys study?
你们在这啊 兄弟们 我还以为把你们弄丢了
There you are, lads. Ha. Thought I'd lost you.
那我怎么办 悲伤一人
Then where would I be? Sad and alone.
晚上好 先生们
Evening, gents.
看来你们已经见过我的门徒了
I see you've met my protégés.
我是迪克兰帕德里克 奥罗修斯麦马努斯教授
I'm Professor Declan Patrick Aloysius MacManus.
幸会 认识你们很荣幸
At your service. I assure you, the pleasure is mine.
但是我必须提醒你们 这几位小伙子是牛津最优秀的学生
But, I must tell you, these lads here were the best of the best at Oxford itself.
我们只是来喝点酒 叙叙旧
And now, we're just having a wee liquid reunion, aren't we?
-牛津  -你是哪个系的教授
-Oxford? -Yeah, what were you professor of?
我退休前教经济管理学
Economics and management, till I retired.
在牛津大学
At Oxford.
没错
That is correct.
我们也是牛津的校友
We were at Oxford.
基督堂学院
Christ Church.
你是哪个学院呢
Which college were you?
基督堂学院
Christ Church?
我们的死敌啊
Our main rivals.
在下是墨顿学院的
I'm a Merton man, myself.
墨顿学院
Merton.
你住在哪里
Where'd you live?
就在教堂对面
Right across from the chapel.
没什么比每天早上8点15分 伴着多布森管风琴的声音醒来更好的
Nothing like waking up every morning to the sound of the Dobson Organ at 8:15,
对吗
am I right?
你这个墨顿的混蛋
You Merton motherfucker.
你好吗 先生 你是哪一年离校的
How are you, sir? When did you leave?
2015年 我们在赛艇比赛中 击败剑桥的那年
2015. The year we beat Cambridge in the boat race
是赢了六个半艇身长 可别忘了
by six and a half lengths, lest we forget.
我就是当时的赛艇队参赛队员 我是舵手
I was on that crew. I was the cox.
可不是嘛 你这个混蛋
Yes, you were, you bastard.
哈里吉尔在这里 哈里吉尔竟然在这间酒吧
Harry Gill is here! Harry Gill, in this pub!
嘿
Hey!
真棒啊…
Marvelous. Marvelous.
麦格教授教了我们很多东西
Professor McGonagall taught us a lot.
但我们学到最重要的东西是金钱的价值
But the main thing he taught us was the value of money.
20英镑 说定了
£20. You're on.
我有…
I got it. I got it.
我有5英镑
I've got five.
-留下买烤肉串 -还需要吗
Save one for a kebab.
一帮怪胎天才
Eccentric geniuses.
是
Right.
17、18、19、20
17, 18, 19, 20.
这个三角学算得怎么样
How's that for trigonometry?
可以的
We got there.
太好了
Yes!
-这球不错 -好样的
-Fair play! -Good on you.
下一轮…我们请
Next round is on us.
随便点
Anything you like.
-装满三个靴子的麦芽酒  -这家伙
-Three big boots of ale? -This guy.
喂 你对牛津怎么这么了解
Oi. How'd you know all that stuff about Oxford?
我曾和一位牛津教授交往 而且我是一个多听少言的人
I dated a professor at Oxford. And I listen more than I talk.
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
喂
Oi.
你真是个传奇
What a legend you are!
很难把这样的一场比赛抛在脑后
Hard to forget a game like that.
你知道怎样做会有帮助吗  去找你爱的女人
You know what will help? Going to see the woman you love.
没错 但我认为 很明显
Exactly. But it's clear to me
彼尔德教练认为自己配不上简
that Coach Beard doesn't think he's worthy of Jane.
是啊
I know.
彼尔德的自尊心太低了 就连自杀都需要别人给他打气
Beard's self-esteem is so low, he will need a pep talk to kill himself,
我很愿意为他打气
and I would like to give that pep talk.
闭嘴吧 蒂埃里亨利
Shut up, Thierry Henry.
真该死
Goddamn fucking shit!
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem here?
是 你的这张跳蚤市场买来的 假波斯咖啡桌上的钉子
Yeah. This nail on your faux Persian flea market coffee table
把我的裤子刮破了
just tore my pants.
先生 请出示你的会员证 谢谢
Sir, can I see your membership card, please?
我的朋友都在里面
My friends are in there.
该死的
Goddamn it.
你应该知道你的裤子破了吧
I'm sure you know that your trousers are ripped.
原本的设计就是这样
They're designed that way.
为了让人更好地拍我马屁
To make it easier for people to kiss my ass.
要小心 我们英国有惩罚衣冠不整的法律
Be careful. We have decency laws in England.
你会被逮捕的
You'll get arrested.
我没意识到这里的法律如此严格
I wasn't aware the laws were so restrictive here.
是 我们是一个压抑人性的国家
Oh, yeah. We're a repressed nation.
一个暴露的屁股就能摧毁君主政体
One exposed arse can bring down the monarchy itself.
你怎么能这样说安德鲁王子
How dare you speak of Prince Andrew that way.
我可以为你补好裤子
I could fix those for you.
我就住在那边
I live over there.
那栋尖顶的建筑
In that pointy building?
不
No.
把裤子脱了
Take your trousers off.
你不是我的老板
You're not in charge of me.
缝补时我会给你裤子穿的
I'll give you something to wear in the meantime.
我的生命中总是有人来来往往
People come and go from my life.
我总会保留他们的一条裤子
I've always kept a pair of their trousers.
这个衣架就像我的回忆录
This rack is like my memoirs.
这一条应该合适
These should fit.
这是谁的
Whose were these?
一位旧情人
An old lover.
他现在在哪
Where's he now?
死了
Dead.
你的钥匙掉了
You dropped your keys.
你是否曾回忆一段感情 后悔它结束了
You ever look back on a relationship and regret it had ended?
我一整天都在这么想
Been doing it all day.
我爱过生命中的每一个男人
I've loved every man in my life,
但我不后悔任何一段感情的结束
but I don't think I regret a single one of those relationships ending.
在我所有最快乐的回忆中 我都是单身
In all my happiest memories, I'm single.
这让我觉得不安
That troubles me.
你曾陷入爱河吗
Have you ever been in love?
现在我的生活中有一个人 她…
I mean, there's someone in my life now who…
也许是化学反应或费洛蒙 但…
maybe it's chemicals or maybe it's pheromones, but…
我想每分每秒都和她在一起
I wanna be with her all the time.
那是爱吗 还是说我有毛病
Is that love, or do I just have a problem?
不可以两个都是吗
Why can't it be both?
你能接一下吗
Could you get that?
显示“别接”
It says, "Do not answer."
那是开玩笑的
It's a joke.
喂 宝贝 我到了 但我忘带钥匙了
Oi, babe, I'm here, but I forgot my keys.
你是谁啊
Who the fuck are you?
我是彼尔德
I'm Beard.
他只是个没长裤的男人 我在骨头与蜜糖认识的
He's just a trouserless man I met at Bones & Honey.
搞什么
What the fuck?
喂 混蛋
Oi, shithead!
我要把你打得满地找牙
I'm gonna punch your fucking teeth out your face
然后再把你的牙塞进你的屁眼 像喂糖一样
and feed 'em to your arsehole like they're candy.
糟了
Oh, shit.
-你应该提醒我一声的 -别介意他
-You could've warned me. -Don't mind him.
他只是有点吃醋
He's just a little jealous.
快开门 你死定了
Open the fucking door. You're a dead man.
快跑
Run.
那家伙在哪
Where the fuck is he?
无处可逃了
Nowhere to go.
喂
Oi!
（N22号：牛津圆环 里士满 富威尔 往里士满）
宝刀未老
Still got it!
喂 他没买票
Oi, he hasn't tapped in.
你不买票 我们就不开车
We're not going anywhere until you tap in.
当然…没问题
Of course, of course, of course. My pleasure.
不好意思 这位女士
Excuse me, madam.
滚开 该死的乞丐
Piss off, you fucking scrounger.
（艾弗里詹姆斯酒店）
晚上好 先生
Good evening, sir.
您今晚打算入住酒店吗
Are you staying with us tonight?
不…
No. No, I am not.
明白 祝你晚安
Well. Have a good evening.
我能借用电话吗
Could I please use the phone?
酒店电话只供客人使用 不好意思 先生
The hotel phones are just for guests, I'm afraid, sir.
那好吧
Okay then.
-我能借用你的手机吗  -我的私人手机
-Could I please use your phone? -My personal phone?
对 我的手机和钱包丢了 我只是想回家
Yes, I lost my phone and my wallet, and I'm just trying to get back home.
你打算用我的手机做什么呢 先生
And what would you be using my personal phone for, sir?
预约德士
Booking a cab.
不 我不会上当的
Nope. I'm not falling for that.
我不是在骗你
I'm not trying to trick you.
骗子才会这么说
Exactly what a trickster would say.
我只会通过我自己的账户叫车
I would just go through my own account, you know.
就是这样开始的 对吧 你先预约德士
That's how it starts, isn't it? First you book a cab.
然后你把我的手机连接到你的网络上
Next thing I know, you've geolinked my phone to your network
突然之间 你和假的梅拉尼娅 下载了我所有的银行资料
and all of a sudden, you and fake Melania have downloaded all my bank details
接着你用我的身份
and you're using my identity to shift
将更多罂粟种子转移至你的私人岛屿
more poppy seeds to your own private island.
不 今晚别想
No. Not tonight.
我在这行干得够久了
I've been in this game too long now.
-哪行  -你别想碰我的手机
-What game? -You won't touch my phone.
因为你会在几秒内得知我母亲的娘家姓
Within seconds, you'll have my mother's maiden name,
盗走我的所有加密币
all my cryptocurrencies.
不过我可没有
Not that I have any.
接下来 军情五处将没收我的硬盘
Next thing I know, my hard drive is being confiscated by MI5
因为你骗我下载了非法图片
for illegal images that you've tricked me into downloading.
别想了 你别想耍我
Oh, no. You'll not make a fool of me.
你不行 就算是和朱迪丹奇女爵 长得一样的人也不行
Not you. Not a dead ringer for Dame Judi Dench.
任何人都不行 真为你感到羞愧 先生 晚安
Not anyone. Shame on you, sir! Good night.
有人吗
Hello.
嘿 抱歉打扰你们
Hey, I'm sorry to bother you guys.
我想回家 但我的手机丢了
Just trying to get home and I lost my phone.
还好遇到了你们
You guys are about to save my life.
完了
Ah, shit.
瞧瞧是哪位贵客啊
Well, look who it isn't.
很高兴又见面了 塔特先生
Good to see you again, Mr. Tartt.
之前的事很抱歉 我还是不打扰你们…
Sorry about before. Why don't I let you get back to what you were doing--
没关系 别急嘛
It's okay. There's no rush.
这样吧 兄弟们
I tell you what, lads.
不如我们给穿着大花裤子的教练上一堂课
Why don't we teach Coach here, in his magic trousers…
让他知道什么才是足球
exactly what football's all about.
因为足球的精髓不在球场上
Because it doesn't happen on the pitch.
对
No.
而是在街上
It happens on the street.
懂了吗
You get me?
或者…
Or…
抓住他
Get him!
快点
Come on!
看来彼尔德完蛋了 对吧
Well, it looks like Beard's done for, doesn't it?
盖瑞 我内心有一部分认为 彼尔德今晚很想被揍一顿
Gary, part of me thinks Beard really wanted to get beat up tonight.
绝对的 蒂埃里
Absolutely, Thierry.
他显然更愿意惩罚自己
Clearly he'd rather punish himself
而不是接受身边人的爱和帮助
than accept the love and support of the people around him.
我开始怀疑彼尔德教练厌恶自己了
I'm beginning to think Coach Beard hates himself.
闭嘴吧 蒂埃里亨利
Shut up, Thierry Henry.
怎么样 哥们
Huh, mate?
-再揍他一拳 -混蛋
-Punch him again. -Prick!
你什么都不是
You're nothing!
我揍死你
Gotcha!
给我趴着吧
Stay down!
见鬼
Oh, shit.
-我让你趴… -各位
-I told you to stay-- -Fellas!
不如我们算打平手吧
How about we call this a draw?
你非要逼我们 是吧
You had to push it, didn't ya?
说晚安吧 小子
Say good night, son.
天啊 拜托
Ah, man. Come on.
什么都没发生 她只是要帮我补裤子
Nothing happened. She was just gonna fix my pants.
不…
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
你把这些落在我们家了
You left these at our flat.
我一直想找到你
Been trying to find ya.
谢谢了
Well, that's nice.
不 很抱歉我发脾气了
No, I'm sorry I lost my temper.
玛莉解释了发生了什么
Mary explained what happened.
其实我们要有孩子了
The truth is we're having a baby.
这让我意识到她对我而言多重要
And it's made me realize how precious she is to me,
想到她背着我出轨 我实在是受不了
and the thought that she was cheating on me was just too much.
我懂
Uh-huh.
但我也意识到
But I also realize that
在这件事上 也许我的猜忌心比其他人更重
maybe I'm more paranoid than most when it comes to that.
因为我以前也出过轨
'Cause I used to cheat in the past.
但我真的努力去改变了
But I've really worked on it.
-现在我已经好多了 -那真好
-I'm in a really good place now. -That's great.
是 谢谢
Yeah, cheers.
总之 我只是想把你的东西还给你
Anyway, I just wanted to give you your stuff back.
不过玛莉说她要留下你的裤子
Mary says she's keeping your trousers though.
那是她的习惯
It's kind of her thing.
她说你可以留下这条裤子
She said you can keep those.
-谢谢 -你穿起来很好看
-Thank you. -Well, they look good on you.
我知道
I know.
关于今天比赛的糟糕结果 我很遗憾
Sorry about the shit game today.
我都不是里士满的球迷 但是 我的娘 这场比赛太惨了
And I'm not even a Richmond fan, but, mamma mia, that was tough to watch.
你的钥匙掉了
I think you dropped those.
好的
All right.
祝你一切顺利
You be lucky, yeah?
希望吧
I'm trying.
（52条短信 72个未接电话）
不好 完了…
Oh, no. No, no. No, no, no, no, no, no.
不好…
Oh, no. No, no, no.
（我确实爱你 我说了我爱你）
（我正在做你要求的事 去死吧 彼尔德）
我也爱你…
I love you too. I love you too!
不要啊…
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! No! No! No!
（网上 憎恨）
（意大利面 所有酱料都享有平等待遇）
（全新的美味）
（史上最佳可乐 ）
（曼城 5 AFC里士满 0）
喂 武士
Oi, samurai!
我们叫了豪华轿车…
We got a limo We got a limo
-快上车 来呀 -瞧 我们叫了豪华轿车
-Get in! Come on! -Look, we got a limo!
那几个人其实很好
They were really nice guys in the end.
但桌球技术很烂
And so bad at pool.
我们把真实身份告诉他们了
We told them who we really were,
他们还是邀请我们复活节时 去他们的乡间别墅做客
and they still invited us to their country estate for Easter.
我不知道该穿什么去
I don't know what I'm gonna wear.
我们赢了他们好多钱 所以叫了豪华轿车 享受享受
We made so much money off them, we treated ourself to a limo!
-请问去哪 先生  -哪都行
-Where to, sir? -Anywhere you want.
今晚永不结束
This night will never end.
送我回家吧
Home, please.
谢谢你给了我们一个超棒的夜晚
Thanks for a wicked night.
你们去这个地址
You're gonna go to this address
然后告诉瑞尼 彼尔德说可以
and you're gonna tell Renee that Beard said it was okay.
谢谢你们
Thanks, guys.
只需要一个可爱多
Just one Cornetto
给我
Give it to me
美味的冰淇淋
Delicious ice cream
来自意大利
Of Italy
不
No.
No!
你在吗 上帝
Are you there, God?
是我 玛格丽特的儿子
It's me, Margaret's little boy.
聆听多时 第一次祈祷 我知道你大概很忙
Longtime listener, first-time caller. And I know you're probably busy,
因为你还要处理更重要的事情
'cause you got bigger fish to multiply and then fry.
这是你的工作 但是有个女孩
As you do. But there's this girl.
有个女人 她叫简
There's this woman, Jane.
姓佩恩 佩服的佩 感恩的恩
Last name Payne. P-A-Y-N-E.
但你应该已经知道了 不过这是方便你查找她
But you probably know that, but if you wanted to look her up.
我喜欢她 很喜欢
And I care for her, deeply.
我今晚本可以和她在一起 但结果却和你在一起
I could've been with her tonight, but I ended up with you.
我并不妄想她能缓解我的痛苦
And I am under no illusions that she could solve what ails me.
但每当我和她在一起时 世界就变得…
But when I'm with her, the world just feels…
更有趣
more interesting.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这里 237
Here. 2-3-7.
（严禁进入）
-敲门啊 -为什么你不敲
-Well, knock then. -Why don't you knock?
敲门啊
Just knock.
什么事
What?
你是瑞尼吗
Are you Renee?
你们是谁
Who's asking?
是彼尔德教练让我们来的
Coach Beard sent us.
开灯
Turn 'em on.
这边
Walk this way.
走啊
Go on.
走吧
Come on.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
太美了
It's beautiful.
这是天堂吗
Is that heaven?
不 这是内尔森路体育馆
No. That's Nelson Road.
向观众挥手致意…
Wave to the crowd! Wave to the crowd!
好耶
Yeah!
太棒了
Fuck yes!
试试这个
Try this on.
-这里有吃的  -专为我准备的
-They do food here? -For me, yeah.
-他到底去哪了  -如果彼尔德不来 那我去买咖啡吧
-Where the fuck is he? -If Beard's not coming, I'll get coffees.
等等 别急 他会来的
Wait. Now, hold on a second. He'll be here.
彼尔德就像邮差
Beard's like the mailman, you know?
晴天雨天 永不缺席 而且穿短裤很帅
He always delivers and he looks great in shorts.
早上好 各位
Morning, fellas.
-我说得没错吧  -给
-What'd I tell you? -Here you go.
馥芮白、黑咖啡、薄荷拿铁
Flat white. Coffee, black. Peppermint latte.
谢谢
Cheers.
谢谢你 教练
Thank you, Coach.
你…
You…
一切都好吧
Everything all right, you know?
是 睡得太晚了 肯定是摔下床了
Yeah. Just slept too late. Must've fell off the bed.
是 这很常见
Oh, right. Yeah, no. That's a thing.
好 谁准备好看昨天的比赛了
Okay, who's ready to watch yesterday's match?
-不… -我其实看了好多次了
-No. No. -I've actually watched it plenty.
-我们还是别看了 没必要 -嘿 听我说 我懂的…
-Don't think we should. We don't need to. -Hey, now, look. I know, I know, I know.
-但这样才能进步 对吗  -好吧
-But this is how we get better, all right? -Fine.
因为有时人难免会遇到 一场表现糟糕的比赛 如此…
'Cause sometimes, every once in a blue moon, there is a game so awful, so…
烂得如同一团狗屎
Dog shit?
烂得让人难以释怀
Haunting?
堪比一场巨大的灾难
A catastrophe of epic proportions.
以致于回看比赛的唯一方式 就是用十倍速播放
That the only way to watch it back is at ten times the speed
配上《本尼希尔秀》主题曲 作为背景音乐 来吧
and with the Benny Hill theme music playing under it. Here we go.
要命啊
Fucking hell.
老天爷
好吧
Okay.
（胜利永驻）
（相信）
（#我们是里士满）
字幕翻译：易晗